Hello.
I'm Autolori and I'm from Scaraback 46.
I'm Kira Matsumoto.
We are now
We're at Lovita airport.
We are going to a place called Cantu in Australia
We are going to a place called Cantu in Australia.
It's a long flight.
I'd like to introduce you to my travel companion
I'd like to introduce my travel companion.
DODON!
What did I say?
Yes, I know, you were also in the same boat.
Me too
I like it.
It's a very unique shape.
I got this.
I don't know who gave it to me.
It was given to me by another woman.
That's right.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
YouTube channel.
Since we're just getting started.
I'm sure.
What?
The Are
Eh, eh, eh, eh.
Oh, you're going this far?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, are we going this far?
Watch out!
Watch out! Watch out!
Oh, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared!Oh, scary, scary, scary!
They filmed it for YouTube.
What, YouTube?
YouTube?
Ladies and gentlemen, ZONO says he's going to jump in after this, so stay tuned.
I'll do my best.
I'm going in!
You should see the look on your face when you do that.
All right.
Here we go.
Heh heh heh, I'm in!
Oh!
I'm going to cut the salt.
Yummy!
Delicious!
Yes, sir.
It was so beautiful.
It really was.
The world under the sea
You can't see the top
I feel more like I'm at the bottom of the ocean
I feel like I'm at the bottom of the ocean.
Ear removal
It was very difficult.
Thank you for watching.
See you later.
Is she pink? Red? Red? He's got a thing called "red something, black something.
She'll answer you in a minute.
He seems annoyed.
Shut up.
I wish we could have gotten to know each other better.
It's so much faster than Japan.
I guess you have to see it to believe it.
That's for sure.
All right!Yay!
Oh, I'm scared! I'm so scared!
I'm just plain scared.
I'm so scared!
It's like... it's more open than the Ferris wheel in Japan.
It feels more open than the Ferris wheel in Japan.
Oh, scary! I'm so scared!
It's just plain scary.
It's scary as hell.
I'm a little scared, but not too much.
I might be pretty scared.
It's shaking.
Has it stopped?
Oh, now the guy downstairs is shaking again.
That's it.
Can you see it?
Oh, my God! It's moving!
It's shaking so much.
It's like it's going around and around.
Oh, my God.
Maybe it's stabilized.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, shit, there's some tea left.
Pappa-pappa
Pow.
Heh heh heh.
I'm so happy!
It's over!
I was in there not as fast as I thought I would be, but it was fun.
I'm here.
Uh, Japanese.
I'll show you the source of Japanese.
Here we go!
Old
Year ZoneYEAR ZONE
Sen!
Cherry blossom?
Is this a tree of the Carey-Foltz tree?
A carrifolz tree?
Yes, yes, yes.
A carry-along tree?
Cherry tree?
No.
The carrie-folz tree?
I don't think it's a cherry tree.
Japanese.
cherry tree
Zaca
Me, me, me, me
I, I, I, I
Touch Touch
Me, touch touch
YouTube channel?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Subscribe to our channel.
Subscribe to my channel.
Subscribe to our channel!
Good Button
Good button
And
School
Oh! White chocolate!
Sharp?
White chocolate!
Oh, Yeng!
Sorr-ee-very match.
Sorrry belly match.
Everybody, I'm so squeaky clean!Everyone was so tight!
It was difficult.
It tastes different from Japan.
Winter, it seems to be winter...
It's like the most comfortable feeling on a summer night.
Plus, there's no jibe-jibe feeling.
It's great!
Hey, sis!
Hey, sis.
Did you not hear that?
I wasn't listening. I was listening to her.
We saw a shooting star today.
Hey, sis.
Oh, really?
I want to come back.
Yeah, I'm just barely maxed out.
Better paper, better paper, better paper.
I think we've got it.
Almost there.
Hang in there.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get Kenco here, I promise.
I'm going in there with this big guy.
I'm the biggest guy you've ever seen, and I'm the biggest guy you've ever seen.
Oh! There he is!
There he is!
Whoo-hoo!
I got you!
Oh, my God.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
That's great.
Yo, Thunder.
That was amazing.
I'm getting goosebumps.
We've got two centers in our hearts.
That's what I'm talking about!As one would expect.
Two centers.
Yes, please.
I'm tired. I had to push.
Look, look, look! Who's there?
I flew, like this.
Yes, I'm glad I flew.
I may never fly again.
Good night.
Oh! They just keep coming!
Oh, my gosh.
I forgot it.
Oh, Mar-chan, this song is gone.
You were playing it for us just now.
Look, An-chan's coming out, too.
That's terrible!
Is the theme Sakurazaka?
No, Japanese.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder if it's OK that the big association chose it.
It looks like you can choose your own ice cream.
It's original.
Pinappo Pinappo
Banana banana banana pinappo.
So much ice cream!
Put cookies in it!
Yes!
Wow, wow, wow!
Put a lot of cookies!
Yes!
Wow, wow, wow!
Wow! Fantastic!
What's it like?
Favourite chine!Favourite Chine!
Good!
Are you satisfied?
Yes!
OK!
Two of them matched so beautifully!
There are three colors!
Mango!
AJ, this one!
AJ!
Lychee-ness!
Lychee-ness?
I don't know! I don't know!
Beautiful!
It looks like a mango!
It looks like a salium-colored mango!
I'm sure!
Here's a cookie! Do it!
Have a cookie!
No thanks, cookies!
Christmas!
You're too cute!
I'll show you my face if you don't do it sooner!
Tori...?
No!
No! I can't tell you how frustrated I am.
I'm so annoyed.
It's a snack for my friends.
You're so good at this!
Very good!
I'm satisfied!
Delicious!Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!